Item 28: Your pet name for me.
(Amy:)Time's running out on this.
You need to make a decision.
I submitted you a notarized list.
I'm sorry, but "Gollum"
and "FIakey" are not acceptable.
(Sheldon:)Well, you don't like
"Princess Corncob"
you don't like "Fester,"
you're just impossible to please.
(Amy:)We'll come back to that one.
(Amy:)This brings us to the final item
(Amy:)in our annual
State of the Relationship summit.
Item 29: Valentine's Day.
Ohh! The worst for last.
(Sheldon:)Classic Flakey.
(Amy:)Before you get upset,
(Amy:)I believe I've come up with
a way for us to celebrate
(Amy:)the occasion that we both can enjoy.
(Sheldon:)People usually start
a meeting with a joke,
(Sheldon:)but you go ahead, end with one.
(Amy:)I propose we spend a weekend
(Amy:)at a bed-and-breakfast
in Napa Valley.
(Sheldon:)I hate every word in that sentence.
Including "in" "at," "we" and "a."